[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "__assmate",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Classmate"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "G__db__",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Goodbye"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "G__d morn___",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Good morning"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "Good after____",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Good afternoon"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "Gr__t",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Greet"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "H__lo",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Hello"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "M__itor",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Monitor"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "Te__h_r",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Teacher"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "Fri__d",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Friend"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "G_rd_ner",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Gardener"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "Driv__",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Driver"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "C_a_h",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Coach"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "L__der",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Leader"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "Li___ri_n",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Librarian"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "Engl___",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "Chin__e",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Chinese"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "Ja_it__",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Janitor"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "Stud__t",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Student"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "Pre___t",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Prefect"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "star": 0,
        "score": 20,
        "maxScore": 20,
        "question": "Pr__cip__",
        "questionType": "Text",
        "correctAnswer": "Principal"
    }
]